<?xml version="1.0" encoding="utf-8" standalone="yes"?><rss version="2.0" xmlns:atom="http://www.w3.org/2005/Atom"><channel><title>Posts on Welcome</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/</link><description>Recent content in Posts on Welcome</description><generator>Hugo -- gohugo.io</generator><language>en-us</language><copyright>All rights reserved - 2018</copyright><lastBuildDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:02:30 +0200</lastBuildDate><atom:link href="https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/index.xml" rel="self" type="application/rss+xml"/><item><title>Resting cormorants</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/cormorant-wings-teal-sea/</link><pubDate>Sun, 10 Sep 2017 19:02:30 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/cormorant-wings-teal-sea/</guid><description>![Cormorants resting](/images/large_Show your wings just do it.jpg)
Got this shot of some the shy cormorants with the special teal coloured sea behind. The teal colour is probably due to some algae growth.</description></item><item><title>First light with Sigma 150-600 S</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/sitting-eagle/</link><pubDate>Sun, 16 Apr 2017 19:59:41 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/sitting-eagle/</guid><description>Made this snap of a white-tailed eagle(Haliaeetus albicilla) handheld from a moving boat.
Used Sigma 150-600S on a Canon 60D.
(600mm, 1/1250 s, f/7.1, ISO 500)</description></item><item><title>My workflow for posts</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/site-workflow/</link><pubDate>Thu, 23 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/site-workflow/</guid><description>How the site is updated Here I describe the steps to get a new post on the site. This will serve as my reference for future work.
Prepare images in Lightroom After doing the initial image adjustment I tag them such that they are included in my collection for web. The selected images is exported in smaller dimension and compressed format suitable for the web. The export is saved as a template with image processing settings and export location within my local git working folder.</description></item><item><title>Direct posting via github</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/via-github/</link><pubDate>Sun, 19 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/via-github/</guid><description>Fast publishing This post is entered in a browser on my pad.
Thanks to Hugo using Markdown to format posts I can preview the page before committing the changes.
The purpose is to test how easy I can make new postings to my page.
If auto deploy is working ok the page will be on the web right after I check this in to master.</description></item><item><title>Lyd i bilen etter FM</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/aux-bil/</link><pubDate>Wed, 08 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/aux-bil/</guid><description>I dag slås FM av i Trøndelag og nå er det bare DAB+ som gjelder. Da ble gode råd dyre for meg som hverken har DAB+ eller AUX inn i bilstereoen.
Løsningen Jeg valgte nettradio og monterte en AUX-kabel på multimedia-inngangen bak på anlegget. Jeg slipper dermed å bruke adapter som sender lyden via FM.
Anlegget i min VW Passat fra 2006 er en MFD2-DVD med en 18-pins multimedia-kontakt bak. Her er det mulig å sende inn eksternt lydsignal.</description></item><item><title>A winters night in Steinfjorden</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/vinternatt-steinfjorden/</link><pubDate>Fri, 03 Feb 2017 00:00:00 +0000</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/vinternatt-steinfjorden/</guid><description>Catched the snow covered and moon lit mountains in December 2016.</description></item><item><title>Small IoT project</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/arduino-mqtt/</link><pubDate>Wed, 01 Feb 2017 10:54:24 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/arduino-mqtt/</guid><description>To start learning the mechanisms for IoT I have a simple environment monitoring project.
First steps is to establish temperature/humidity measurement and publishing these via MQTT.</description></item><item><title>My First Post</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/first-post/</link><pubDate>Sun, 29 Jan 2017 11:17:35 +0100</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/first-post/</guid><description>Testing Hugo to generate static pages.
Welcome Function Here is a little Python function to welcome you:
def hello_world(): print &amp;#34;Hello there!&amp;#34;</description></item><item><title>Leilighet til leie, Reppevegen 90 B</title><link>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/utleie/</link><pubDate>Fri, 17 Jun 2016 15:49:57 +0200</pubDate><guid>https://hholi.github.io/hugoweb/post/utleie/</guid><description>Leiligheten er på 44 kvadratmeter og inneholder lunt og trivelig flislagt bad med varmekabler i gulv. Eget vaskerom/bod med lagerplass og plass til tørkestativ. Vaskerommet inneholder hylleplass, skyllekum og ny vaskemaskin, 8kg, ekstra fokus på lavt støynivå og energibesparing.
Fra soverommet har du utsikt ut over fjorden. Soverommet har nytt klesskap med speil og skyvedører.
Stue, kjøkken og inngangsparti har varmekabler i gulv og lyse vegger, tak og gulv. Fra stuevinduet kan du skue ut over Trondheimsfjorden og du kan se både Gråkallen, Tyholttårnet og Munkholmen fra godstolen der.</description></item></channel></rss>